Jhaal, let's
learn how to
print or email the insurance policy. First,
click on the insurance option and click on this track. On
clicking it, the
approved policy number will
appear on the screen like this. On
clicking this policy, you will
see all the policy details.
Click on this button here. On
clicking the next button, an
OTP will appear on the customer's registered number. Enter the OTP here.
After successful OTP verification, subscribe to the two-
wheeler insurance policy in this way. By
clicking on the pen, the OTP will be downloaded.
You can print it and email it
to the customer.
We will only give this important information, the Certificate of Insurance,
to the customer, and that too
after a social obligation because this is a very
sensitive document. That's why customers
take some precautions. So, never share this document
with anyone else. In
this way, you
can activate the two-wheeler policy for the customer. Thank you,
Jhaal.